tunngle.net 2016-05-11

# Tunngle - Privacy Policy

**Collection and processing of personal data**

As a rule, you can browse our internet pages without sharing personal data. We only get to know your IP address, the internet site you arrived from, the pages you are calling up and date and length of your visit. We evaluate this information for statistical purposes and to improve our internet pages. Your anonymity as individual user remains protected.

**Usage and sharing of personal data und defined purpose**

All incoming personal data within the context of our service offers are collected, processed and used solely for contract fulfilment and protection of legitimate business interests in terms of consulting, settlement and customer service, in addition to market-oriented product design. The data are used exclusively by Tunngle.net GmbH and associated businesses and will not be shared with third parties unless essential for the fulfilment of a contract entered by you.

**Google analytics**

The web page uses Google analytics, a web analysis service of google Inc. (“google”). Google analytics uses so-called ”cookies“, i.e. text files stored in your computer that allow an analysis of the website’s use by you. The information gleaned from cookies with respect to your use of the website (including IP address) will be transferred to a google server in the USA and stored. Google will use the information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports about website activities for website operators, and to render other services related to your website and internet usage. Google will at times transfer the information to third parties to the extent such action is mandated by law and/or third party information processing at the behest of google. Google will in no case intermingle your IP address with other google data. You may prevent installation of the cookies with a corresponding setting of your browser software; we hasten to point out, though, that in such instance, not all of the website’s functions may be fully operable. By using the website, you consent to the processing of personal data collected by google in the aforementioned manner for the above-referenced purpose.

**Cookies**

Like many other commercial websites, tunngle.net uses the general technology of “cookies“ for the collection of data, thereby making known your habits of using the website, and also to ensure a pleasurable visit on your part. Our cookies do neither reveal nor contain any personal data. Cookies cannot read information in your computer or interact with other cookies on your hard drive. Cookies let us, though, recognise you when revisiting our website. If you do not wish your browser to accept cookies, you can eliminate that possibility in your browser preferences. Shutting off the cookie function may impede the proper functioning of the website, though. As a result, you may not be able to fully exploit all possibilities and information the website has to offer.

**Click-through URL**

In some e-mail messages to our customers, we use a technique known as “click-through URL”. When you click on one of the links, you will reach the actual website through our computer system only. The Tunngle.net GmbH uses these “click-throughs” to determine the interest in certain subjects and measure the effectiveness of our communication setups. These data are not shared with anyone nor will we make any attempt to match these “click-throughs” to individual email addresses.

**Security**

The Tunngle.net GmbH protects its data through technical and organisational measures from illegal access, loss or destruction. We make every effort to improve on a continuing basis our measures at security.

**Hyperlinks to outside internet pages**

The internet pages of the Tunngle.net GmbH contain hyperlinks to those of third-party vendors. Tunngle.net GmbH shall bear no liability for the data protection strategies and content of these outside vendors.

**Your right to know**

As set forth in the Federal Data Protection act (BDSG) you are entitled as user to know which of the data Tunngle.net GmbH has stored under your name or pseudonym. You are free to retract at any time your formerly expressed consent for the future collection, processing and use of your personal data. In such instance, your data will be forthwith deleted.

**Use of Facebook SocialPlug-ins**

On our websites, we use SocialPlug-ins (“Plug-ins”) of the social network facebook.com operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave., Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (Facebook). The plug-ins feature the Facebook logo. A plug-in designates a computer programme to be integrated into another software product, e.g. your browser, for the purpose of enhancing the latter’s performance. The “I like it” button to be found on our web pages represents such a plug-in. When you go to a web page including a plug-in, your browser connects to the Facebook servers. Only upon connection will the plug-in’s functionality be directly transferred to your browser and show up on our web site. The plug-in relays information about your visit from your browser to Facebook. If you are logged in at Facebook while visiting our website, Facebook will assign you to its Facebook identity ledger. When you activate the plug-ins or write a comment, this information will likewise be transferred from your browser to Facebook and stored there. We are not aware of any other data transfers. If you wish to avoid our data’s direct transfers, we recommend visiting our sites only when being logged out of Facebook. You also have the option to protect your browser from plug-ins by installing add-ons to block the integration of plug-ins. Comprehensive information on the collection, storage and use of your data by Facebook and the associated exercise of your rights and protection of your privacy can be found in the Facebook Guidelines for Data Protection.

**Third-party ad serving work**

We're using third-party ad serving. The content of the site comes from Tunngle.net , but the ads come from another server or website. Your browser assembles the differing information fed from differing sources so all items appear on the same page. For your browser to assemble the ads correctly, the website directs your browser to collect information from a different site's ad server. The third party website creates a cookie in your browser's folder as a result. All third-party advertisers are acting independent and be responsible for the delivered ad-content. 

**Why we use third-party ad serving**

Our service depend on advertising to continue operations. We don't have the technical and business development infrastructure to recruit our own advertiser accounts and serve our own ads. As a result, we rely on other websites, third party advertisement serving companies, to recruit advertisers and serve those ads on publishers' sites. This arrangement allows us to focus on what we do best and save time and money.

**Third-party ad serving opt-out**
